Guide to the Roe Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Family Photographs, 1861-1960; Series VI; 3.5' (9 boxes)
  - Roe, Emma Wickham, 1861, 1872, 1884, 1901 (Box 60, Folder 991)
    See also: box 114, folders 1974-1975
  - [Roe, James Gilbert?], undated (Box 60, Folder 992)
  - Roe, Jennie, undated (Box 60, Folder 993)
  - Roe, John Peter, undated (Box 60, Folder 994)
  - Roe, Joseph Wickham and Roe, Nellie Allen, 1872-1903 (Box 60, Folder 995)
    See also: box 114, folders 1976-1979 box 115, folder 1993 box 164, folder 80
  - Roe, Joseph Wickham, 1905-1960 (Box 60, Folder 996-997)
  - Roe, Joseph Wickham and Roe, Mary Lambertson, undated (Box 60, Folder 998)
  - Roe, Julia Morgan, undated (Box 60, Folder 999)
  - Roe, Mary Abigail, 1919, undated (Box 60, Folder 1000)
    See also: box 114, folder 1980
  - Roe, Mary Abigail - women's portraits, undated (Box 60, Folder 1001)
  - Roe, Mary Lambertson, 1916 (Box 60, Folder 1002)
  - Roe, Mary Wickham, 1867-1941 (Box 60, Folder 1003-1005)
  - Roe, Mary Wickham, undated (Box 61, Folder 1006-1007)
  - Roe, Mary Wickham - friends, undated (Box 61, Folder 1008)
  - Roe, Nellie Allen, 1902 (Box 61, Folder 1009)
  - Roe, Peter, undated (Box 61, Folder 1010)
  - Roe, Walter Clark, 1874-1913 (Box 61, Folder 1011-1012)
  - Roe, Walter Clark: Williams College, 1881 (Box 61, Folder 1013-1014)
  - Roe, Walter Clark and Roe, Mary Wickham, undated (Box 61, Folder 1015-1016)
  - Roe, Walter Clark and Roe, Mary Wickham, undated (Box 62, Folder 1017)
  - Roe, Walter Clark and Roe, Mary Wickham - European Tour, 1902 (Box 62, Folder 1018)
  - Roe, William E., 1878, undated (Box 62, Folder 1019)
  - Snell family, 1874, undated (Box 62, Folder 1020)
  - Wickham family, undated (Box 62, Folder 1021)
  - Wickham family: album, undated (Box 62, Folder 1022)
  - Wickham family: friends, undated (Box 62, Folder 1023)
  - Wickham, Elizabeth Mervin, undated (Box 62, Folder 1024-1025)
  - Wickham, Joseph Dresser, 1875, 1887, undated (Box 62, Folder 1026-1027)
    See also: box 115, folder 1981
  - Wickham, Joseph Dresser and Wickham, Elizabeth Merwin, undated (Box 63, Folder 1028)
  - Wood family, undated (Box 63, Folder 1029)
  - Wright, Frank Hall, undated (Box 63, Folder 1030)
  - Unidentified children, undated (Box 63, Folder 1031-1032)
  - Unidentified groups, undated (Box 63, Folder 1033-1034)
  - Unidentified men, undated (Box 63, Folder 1035-1037)
  - Unidentified women, undated (Box 63, Folder 1038-1041)
  - Unidentified women: Binghamton, N.Y., undated (Box 63, Folder 1042)
  - Unidentified women: Los Angeles, undated (Box 63, Folder 1043-1044)
  - Unidentified women: Texas, undated (Box 63, Folder 1045)
  - Houses and interiors, undated (Box 64, Folder 1046)
  - Bermuda, undated (Box 64, Folder 1047-1051)
  - Canada: views of Nova Scotia and Newfoundland, undated (Box 64, Folder 1052-1053)
  - Europe: tour views, 1902-1903 (Box 64, Folder 1054-1056)
  - Jamaica, undated (Box 64, Folder 1057)
  - United States
    - California: views, undated (Box 64, Folder 1058)
    - Florida: views, undated (Box 64, Folder 1059)
    - New Jersey: Atlantic City, undated (Box 65, Folder 1060)
    - New York: Cornwall on the Hudson, undated (Box 65, Folder 1061-1062)
    - Pennsylvania: The Hill School, Pottstown, undated (Box 65, Folder 1063)
    - New Mexico: postcards, undated (Box 65, Folder 1064)
    - Texas: postcards, undated (Box 65, Folder 1065)
    - Vermont: Lake Bomoseen, undated (Box 65, Folder 1066-1067)
    - Vermont: Manchester, undated (Box 65, Folder 1068-1069)
      See also: box 115, folder 1983
    - Vermont: Unidentified views, undated (Box 65, Folder 1070)
    - Western States: photos of tour, 1917 (Box 65, Folder 1071)
    - Wisconsin: Witches' Gulch, undated (Box 65, Folder 1072)
  - Unidentified views, undated (Box 65, Folder 1073-1074)
  - Glass slide: "Adam and Eve in Paradise", undated (Box 65, Folder 1075)
  - Lantern slides of ancient Greece, undated (Box 66, Folder 1076)
- Henry Roe Cloud Papers, 1907-1952; Series VII; 2.25' (6 boxes)
  Series VII, HENRY ROE CLOUD PAPERS, is housed in Boxes 67-72 of the Roe Family Papers. The correspondence has been arranged chronologically, with undated correspondence placed at the end. Box 72, folders 1183-1191, contain various papers, arranged alphabetically by type of material and then chronologically.
  - Correspondence, 1907-1909 (Box 67, Folder 1077-1100)
  - Correspondence, 1910 January-1910 Sep (Box 68, Folder 1101-1119)
  - Correspondence, 1910 October-1911 (Box 69, Folder 1120-1141)
  - Correspondence, 1912-1914 June (Box 70, Folder 1142-1158)
  - Correspondence, 1914 July-1922 (Box 71, Folder 1159-1179)
  - Correspondence, 1924-1952, undated (Box 72, Folder 1180-1182)
  - Memorabilia, 1913, 1924, undated (Box 72, Folder 1183)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1912-1950 (Box 72, Folder 1184-1185)
  - Papers, undated (Box 72, Folder 1186)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 72, Folder 1187)
  - Writings, 1907-1917, undated (Box 72, Folder 1188-1190)
  - Writings: "From Wigwam to Pulpit", 1916 (Box 72, Folder 1191)
- Missionary Correspondence, 1897-1942; Series VIII; 4.25' (10 boxes)
  Series VIII, MISSIONARY CORRESPONDENCE, is located in Boxes 73-82 and consists of the professional correspondences of Walter Clark Roe and Mary Wickham Roe. The correspondence is chronologically arranged, and undated letters have been placed at the end of the series.
  - Correspondence, 1897-1906 (Box 73, Folder 1192-1212)
  - Correspondence, 1907-1908 (Box 74, Folder 1213-1232)
  - Correspondence, 1909 January-1911 February (Box 75, Folder 1233-1258)
  - Correspondence, 1911 March-1913 August (Box 76, Folder 1259-1278)
  - Correspondence, 1913 September-1915 December (Box 77, Folder 1279-1301)
  - Correspondence, 1916-1919 (Box 78, Folder 1302-1326)
  - Correspondence, 1920-1923 (Box 79, Folder 1327-1356)
  - Correspondence, 1924-1927 March (Box 80, Folder 1351-1381)
  - Correspondence, 1927 April-1930 (Box 81, Folder 1382-1408)
  - Correspondence, 1931-1942 (Box 82, Folder 1409-1426)
  - Bussing, Emily A. (Mrs. John S.), undated (Box 82, Folder 1427)
  - Olcott, Kate, undated (Box 82, Folder 1428)
  - "Pardner", undated (Box 82, Folder 1429)
  - Roe, Mary Wickham, undated (Box 82, Folder 1430)
  - Runk, Louise F., undated (Box 82, Folder 1431-1433)
  - Smith, R. Esther, undated (Box 82, Folder 1434)
  - A - D, undated (Box 82, Folder 1435)
  - E - K, undated (Box 82, Folder 1436)
  - L - P, undated (Box 82, Folder 1437)
  - S - Z, undated (Box 82, Folder 1438)
  - Unidentified and fragments, undated (Box 82, Folder 1439)
  - Greeting cards, undated (Box 82, Folder 1440)
- Missionary Papers, 1886-1941; Series IX; 8.0' (20 boxes)
  Boxes 83-102 contain Series IX, MISSIONARY PAPERS, which has been divided into four sections. Section one, North American Missions of the Reformed Church in America (Boxes 83-87), begins with general papers on the mission work of the Reformed Church, arranged alphabetically by type of material. This is followed by papers relating to specific missions, which are arranged alphabetically by name of mission.
  Section two, Other Missions to Indians of North America (Boxes 87-88), and section three, Indians of North America (Boxes 88-97), are both arranged alphabetically by topic. The final section, Missions to the Indians of Latin America (Boxes 98-102), has been divided into two parts. In the first, the material is arranged alphabetically by the name of the mission organization or publication. This is followed by more specific material, which is arranged alphabetically by name of country.
  - North American Missions of the Reformed Church in America
    - Reformed Church in America
      - The Christian Intelligencer and Mission Field, clippings, undated (Box 83, Folder 1441-1443)
      - Classis records, 1911, 1925, undated (Box 83, Folder 1444)
      - The Day-Star, 1907 December (Box 83, Folder 1445)
      - Pamphlets, 1905-1907, undated (Box 83, Folder 1446)
    - Women's Board of Domestic Missions
      - Addresses, 1911, undated (Box 83, Folder 1447)
      - Annual reports, 1906-1914, 1933-1934 (Box 83, Folder 1448-1452)
      - Bulletin, 1933 (Box 83, Folder 1453)
      - History of Christian work, 1932 (Box 83, Folder 1454)
      - History of Indian work, undated (Box 83, Folder 1455)
      - Obituaries of mission workers, 1913-1941, undated (Box 83, Folder 1456-1457)
      - Obituaries of mission workers, 1913, 1922 (Box 84, Folder 1458)
      - Pamphlets
        - General mission, undated (Box 84, Folder 1459-1460)
        - Indian missions, undated (Box 84, Folder 1461-1465)
        - Indian missions (by Mary Wickham Roe), undated (Box 84, Folder 1466)
      - Roe, Mary Wickham - speeches and speech notes, undated (Box 84, Folder 1467-1469)
      - Roe, Walter Clark - speeches and speech notes, undated (Box 84, Folder 1470-1471)
    - Women's Board of Foreign Missions, pamphlets, undated (Box 84, Folder 1472)
    - Colony Mission
      - Articles by Mary Wickham Roe, undated (Box 84, Folder 1473)
      - Camp-meetings, 1900-1922 (Box 84, Folder 1474-1475)
      - Camp-meetings, undated (Box 85, Folder 1476)
      - Circular letters, 1899-1930 (Box 85, Folder 1477-1483)
      - Colony Courier, 1910 March 24 (Box 85, Folder 1484)
      - Conferences of workers, 1906-1912 (Box 85, Folder 1485-1486)
      - Financial accounts, 1909-1913, 1921, n.d (Box 85, Folder 1487-1489)
      - Indian Agency, 1917 (Box 85, Folder 1490)
      - Indian testimonials, undated (Box 85, Folder 1491-1494)
      - Indian wills, 1911-1913 (Box 85, Folder 1495)
      - Newspaper articles by Mary Wickham Roe, 1899-1930 (Box 85, Folder 1496)
      - Newspaper articles by Walter Roe, 1897-1912 (Box 85, Folder 1497)
      - Newspaper clippings from The Pow-Wow and The Day-Star, 1898, undated (Box 85, Folder 1498)
      - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 85, Folder 1499-1501)
      - Notes, undated (Box 86, Folder 1502)
      - Pamphlets by Mary Wickham Roe, undated (Box 86, Folder 1503)
      - Pamphlets by Walter Clark Roe, undated (Box 86, Folder 1504)
      - Pamphlets, undated (Box 86, Folder 1505-1507)
      - Papers, 1912, undated (Box 86, Folder 1508)
      - Session books and reports, 1896-1907 (Box 86, Folder 1509)
    - Comanche Mission-Lawton Station
      - Circular letters, 1900-1939 (Box 86, Folder 1510-1511)
      - Indian testimonials, undated (Box 86, Folder 1512)
      - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 86, Folder 1513)
      - Pamphlets by Richard H. Harper, undated (Box 86, Folder 1514)
      - Pamphlets, undated (Box 86, Folder 1515-1516)
    - Dulce-Jicarilla Mission
      - Circular letters, 1912-1931 (Box 86, Folder 1517-1518)
      - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 86, Folder 1519-1520)
      - Pamphlets by J. Denton Simms, undated (Box 86, Folder 1521)
      - Pamphlets, undated (Box 86, Folder 1522)
      - Records, 1916 (Box 86, Folder 1523)
      - Reports, 1910-1919, undated (Box 86, Folder 1524)
    - Ft. Sill-Apache Mission
      - Newspaper clippings, 1900-1930, undated (Box 86, Folder 1525)
      - Pamphlets, undated (Box 86, Folder 1526)
      - Prisoner relief, 1912-1920 (Box 87, Folder 1527)
      - Reports and records, 1913, undated (Box 87, Folder 1528)
    - Mescalero Mission
      - Circular letters, 1907-1937 (Box 87, Folder 1529)
      - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 87, Folder 1530)
      - Pamphlets, undated (Box 87, Folder 1531-1532)
      - Reports and records, 1911, 1921, undated (Box 87, Folder 1533)
      - Reservation rights, 1913-1916 (Box 87, Folder 1534)
    - Winnebago Mission
      - Circular letters, 1911-1931 (Box 87, Folder 1535)
      - Financial records, 1909-1911 (Box 87, Folder 1536)
      - Indian testimonials, 1909-1911, undated (Box 87, Folder 1537)
      - "The Monthly Recorder", 1913 January-July (Box 87, Folder 1538)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1911-1926, undated (Box 87, Folder 1539-1540)
      - Pamphlets, undated (Box 87, Folder 1541-1542)
      - Papers, 1910-1915, undated (Box 87, Folder 1543)
      - Watermulder, G.A. - papers, 1910, undated (Box 87, Folder 1544)
  - Other Missions to Indians of North America
    - American Missionary Association, undated (Box 87, Folder 1545)
    - Baptist Home Missions, undated (Box 87, Folder 1546)
    - The Christian Indian Company, 1925-1934 (Box 87, Folder 1547)
    - Interchurch World Movement of North America, 1920, undated (Box 87, Folder 1548)
    - Joint Committee on Indian Missions of the Home Missions Council, 1908-1934, undated (Box 87, Folder 1549-1551)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church
      - Publication, 1908 (Box 88, Folder 1552)
      - Women's Home Missions, undated (Box 88, Folder 1553)
    - National Fellowship of Indian Workers, 1935-1937 (Box 88, Folder 1554-1555)
    - National Indian Association
      - The Indian's Friend, 1901-1926 (Box 88, Folder 1556)
      - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 88, Folder 1557)
      - Pamphlets, 1901-1911, undated (Box 88, Folder 1558)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Board of Home Missions
      - Navajo missions, undated (Box 88, Folder 1559)
      - "The Nez Perces since Spalding", 1936 (Box 88, Folder 1560)
      - Pamphlets, undated (Box 88, Folder 1561-1562)
      - Publications, 1908, 1910, 1921,undated (Box 88, Folder 1563)
    - Society for Propagating the Gospel among the Indians and Others in North America, 1932 (Box 88, Folder 1564)
    - Young Men's Christian Association, Indian work, 1914, undated (Box 88, Folder 1565)
    - Miscellaneous and Unidentified Missions to Indians of North America
      - Circular letters, 1904-1919, undated (Box 88, Folder 1566)
      - The Missionary Review of the World, 1915 April-Aug; 1930 April; 1932 January-February (Box 88, Folder 1567-1569)
      - Pamphlets, undated (Box 89, Folder 1570)
      - Publications, 1911, undated (Box 89, Folder 1571)
      - Record of Christian Work, 1929 Nov; 1931 February (Box 89, Folder 1572)
      - The Student Volunteer Movement Bulletin, 1921 January (Box 89, Folder 1573)
  - Indians of North America
    - American Indian Association Conference, 1911 (Box 89, Folder 1574)
    - American Indian Defense Association: pamphlets, 1929-1930 (Box 89, Folder 1575)
    - American Indian Institute
      - The Indian Outlook, 1923-1933 (Box 89, Folder 1576-1580)
      - Pamphlets, 1920-1937, undated (Box 89, Folder 1581)
      - Reports, 1920-1924 (Box 89, Folder 1582)
    - Carlisle Indian School, 1915-1918 (Box 89, Folder 1583)
    - The Chronicles of Oklahoma, 1925 June; 1927 June Dec; 1940 Mar, June (Box 89, Folder 1584-1586)
    - The Chronicles of Oklahoma, 1940 Sep, Dec; 1941 March (Box 90, Folder 1587-1591)
    - The Chronicles of Oklahoma, 1941 June (Box 91, Folder 1592)
    - Dept. of the Interior, Bureau of Indian Affairs
      - Addresses, 1898-1911; 1921-1928 (Box 91, Folder 1593-1595)
      - Annual Reports, 1911, 1915, 1917, 1929, 1932 (Box 91, Folder 1596-1597)
      - Indians at Work, 1934 March-1935 June (Box 91, Folder 1598-1604)
      - Indians at Work, 1935 March-1936 September (Box 92, Folder 1605-1617)
      - Indians at Work, 1936 October-1941 February (Box 93, Folder 1618-1634)
      - Informational Bulletins, 1910-1929, undated (Box 94, Folder 1635-1637)
      - Magazine articles, 1909-1939, undated (Box 94, Folder 1638)
      - Magazine reprints, 1923-1935, undated (Box 94, Folder 1639)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1903-1924, undated (Box 94, Folder 1640-1643)
      - Policy papers, undated (Box 94, Folder 1644)
    - Folklore, undated (Box 94, Folder 1645)
    - Hampton Institute
      - Publications, undated (Box 94, Folder 1646)
      - Student essays, 1913 (Box 94, Folder 1647-1649)
    - Haskell Institute
      - The Indian Leader, 1923-1928 (Box 94, Folder 1650)
      - "The Y.M.C.A. Bulletin", 1914-1921 (Box 94, Folder 1651)
    - History and Culture
      - Advertisements, undated (Box 94, Folder 1652-1653)
      - Bulletin of the American Museum of Natural History, 1904 May, 1907 May (Box 94, Folder 1654)
      - Daughters of the American Revolution, resolutions, 1920's (Box 94, Folder 1655)
      - Education: essays, 1912, undated (Box 94, Folder 1656)
      - Essays, undated (Box 94, Folder 1657)
      - Indian Legends, trans. M.D. Harris, 1901 (Box 95, Folder 1658)
      - Magazine clippings, 1901-1923, undated (Box 95, Folder 1659-1660)
      - Magazines
        - Art and Archaeology, 1918 January-February (Box 95, Folder 1661)
        - Out West, 1912 February (Box 95, Folder 1662)
        - Peoples of All Nations, 1922 August (Box 95, Folder 1663)
        - Records of the Past, 1914 March (Box 95, Folder 1664)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1886-1937, undated (Box 95, Folder 1665-1671)
      - Pamphlets, 1905-1932, undated (Box 95, Folder 1672-1674)
      - Poetry, undated (Box 95, Folder 1675)
      - Scrapbook, undated (Box 96, Folder 1676)
      - Sign language notes, undated (Box 96, Folder 1677)
    - Indian Board of Co-operation of California, 1920, 1925, undated (Box 96, Folder 1678)
    - Indian Rights Association
      - Indian Truth, 1924-1937 (Box 96, Folder 1679-1680)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1925, undated (Box 96, Folder 1681)
      - Publications, 1893-1936 (Box 96, Folder 1682-1683)
    - Indian School Journal, 1920, 1923 (Box 96, Folder 1684)
    - Lake Mohonk Conferences on the Indian, 1898, 1905, 1906, 1929 (Box 96, Folder 1685-1687)
    - Mohonk Lodge
      - Account books, 1905, undated (Box 96, Folder 1688)
      - Bills and receipts, 1911-1931 (Box 97, Folder 1689)
      - Catalogues, undated (Box 97, Folder 1690)
      - Circular letters, 1908-1916, undated (Box 97, Folder 1691)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1888-1889, 1912 (Box 97, Folder 1692)
      - Pamphlets, undated (Box 97, Folder 1693)
    - National American Indian Memorial, 1913 (Box 97, Folder 1694)
    - National Indian Student Conference, 1914 (Box 97, Folder 1695)
    - "New Trends in Indian Education" Progressive Education, 1932 February (Box 97, Folder 1696)
    - The Oklahoma Indian School Magazine, 1932 March-April (Box 97, Folder 1697)
    - Peyote cult, 1918, 1937, n.d (Box 97, Folder 1698)
    - Reservation maps, 1920, 1923 (Box 97, Folder 1699)
    - Roe Indian Institute, 1915, undated (Box 97, Folder 1700)
    - Santee Normal Training School, 1910-1936, undated (Box 97, Folder 1701-1702)
      - The American Indian Magazine, 1917-1920 (Box 97, Folder 1704-1705)
    - Seger, John H., (1846-1928) (Box 97, Folder 1703)
    - Society of American Indians
      - Pamphlets, undated (Box 97, Folder 1706)
    - World War I newspaper clippings, 1918-1919, undated (Box 97, Folder 1707-1709)
  - Missions to the Indians of Latin America
    - The Central American Bulletin, 1923-1926, 1935 (Box 98, Folder 1710-1711)
    - Commission on Indian Work in Latin America, undated (Box 98, Folder 1712)
    - Committee on Co-Operation in Latin America
      - Annual reports, 1923, 1926, 1930 (Box 98, Folder 1713)
      - Bulletins, 1925-1937 (Box 98, Folder 1714)
      - Circular letters, 1922, 1932 (Box 98, Folder 1715)
      - Congresses on Christian Work, 1915-1925 (Box 98, Folder 1716)
      - Pamphlets, 1925, 1928, undated (Box 98, Folder 1717)
    - Inland South America Missionary Union
      - Amazon Valley Indian, 1937 January-March (Box 98, Folder 1718)
      - Circular letters, 1911-1916 (Box 98, Folder 1719)
      - Inland South America, 1922-1927 (Box 98, Folder 1720)
      - Pamphlets, undated (Box 98, Folder 1721)
      - South America's Indians, 1910-1914 (Box 98, Folder 1722-1724)
    - The Latin American Evangelist, 1920-1927, 1933 (Box 98, Folder 1725-1726)
    - The Latin American Prayer Fellowship News, 1932-1934, undated (Box 98, Folder 1727)
    - The Pan-American Union: pamphlets, 1910-1923 (Box 98, Folder 1728-1729)
    - The Pan-American Union: pamphlets, undated (Box 99, Folder 1730)
    - Pioneer Mission Agency
      - Circular letters, 1926-1934, undated (Box 99, Folder 1731)
      - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 99, Folder 1732)
      - Pamphlets, 1924-1936, undated (Box 99, Folder 1733)
      - Pioneer News, 1926-1936 (Box 99, Folder 1734)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Board of Foreign Missions
      - Annual report on Latin American missions, 1926 (Box 99, Folder 1735)
      - Circular letters, 1925 (Box 99, Folder 1736-1737)
    - World Dominion Survey, 1927 (Box 99, Folder 1738)
    - Latin America general
      - Magazine clippings, 1906-1910, 1922-1931, undated (Box 99, Folder 1739-1742)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1915-1932, undated (Box 99, Folder 1743-1744)
    - Argentina, 1924, undated (Box 99, Folder 1745)
    - Bolivia, 1925-1940 (Box 99, Folder 1746)
    - Brazil
      - Articles, 1923-1928, undated (Box 99, Folder 1747)
      - Circular letters, 1926-1935, undated (Box 99, Folder 1748)
      - Pamphlet, undated (Box 99, Folder 1749)
    - Chile, circular letters, 1926-1933 (Box 99, Folder 1750)
    - Colombia
      - Circular letters, 1922-1933 (Box 99, Folder 1751-1753)
      - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 99, Folder 1754)
    - Costa Rica, circular letters, 1932 (Box 99, Folder 1755)
    - Guatemala
      - The Cachiquel News, 1922-1937 (Box 100, Folder 1756)
      - Chiquimula Mission, undated (Box 100, Folder 1757)
      - Circular letters, 1929-1937 (Box 100, Folder 1758)
      - Corazon Y vida, 1923-1927 (Box 100, Folder 1759)
      - Guatemala News, 1922-1937 (Box 100, Folder 1760-1768)
      - The Harvester, 1923-1940 (Box 100, Folder 1768)
      - El Mensajero, 1926-1932 (Box 100, Folder 1769)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1922-1931, undated (Box 100, Folder 1770-1771)
      - Pamphlets, 1919-1937, undated (Box 100, Folder 1772-1773)
    - Honduras, map, undated (Box 100, Folder 1774)
    - Mexico
      - Missions of the Reformed Church in America in Mexico
        - Addresses, undated (Box 100, Folder 1775)
        - Circular letters, 1923-1935 (Box 100, Folder 1776)
        - Goodwill mission of Mary Wickham Roe, 1926 (Box 100, Folder 1777)
        - Newspaper clippings, 1924-1930, undated (Box 101, Folder 1778-1779)
        - Pamphlets, 1928-1932, undated (Box 101, Folder 1780-1781)
        - Papers, undated (Box 101, Folder 1782)
      - Missions in Mexico
        - Articles, 1922-1935, undated (Box 101, Folder 1783-1784)
        - Circular letters, 1926-1938 (Box 101, Folder 1785)
        - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 101, Folder 1786)
        - Pamphlets, 1929, undated (Box 101, Folder 1787)
      - General
        - Articles, 1913-1930, undated (Box 101, Folder 1788-1789)
        - Bibliographies, undated (Box 101, Folder 1790)
        - Magazines, 1910, 1924-1928 (Box 101, Folder 1791)
    - Mexican Folk-ways, 1926-1927 (Box 101, Folder 1792)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1916-1928, undated (Box 101, Folder 1793-1795)
    - "Notes on the Indians of Sonora, Mexico", undated (Box 101, Folder 1796)
    - Press Releases, 1926-1928 (Box 101, Folder 1797)
    - Publications of the Department of Education, 1925, 1927 (Box 102, Folder 1798)
    - Publications of La Universidad National, 1924-1930 (Box 102, Folder 1799-1800)
    - Travel brochures, 1925, undated (Box 102, Folder 1801)
  - Panama - articles, undated (Box 102, Folder 1802)
  - Peru - articles, 1906, undated (Box 102, Folder 1803)
  - Uruguay - Bulletin Diario, 1925 (Box 102, Folder 1804)
  - Venezuela - circular letters, 1923 (Box 102, Folder 1805)
- Missionary Photographs, 1860-1940; Series X; 6.5' (13 boxes)